<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour_Guide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="acropolis_short_desc">The Acropolis of Athens and its monuments are universal
        symbols of the classical spirit and civilization</string>
    <string name="acropolis_desc">The Acropolis of Athens and its monuments are universal
        symbols of the classical spirit and civilization and form the greatest architectural and artistic complex
        bequeathed by Greek Antiquity to the world. In the second half of the fifth century bc, Athens,
        following the victory against the Persians and the establishment of democracy,
        took a leading position amongst the other city-states of the ancient world.
        In the age that followed, as thought and art flourished, an exceptional group of
        artists put into effect the ambitious plans of Athenian statesman Pericles and, under the inspired guidance of
        the sculptor Pheidias, transformed the rocky hill into a unique monument of thought and the arts.
        The most important monuments were built during that time: the Parthenon, built by Ictinus, the Erechtheon
        , the Propylaea, the monumental entrance to the Acropolis, designed by Mnesicles and the small temple Athena Nike.
    </string>
<string name="acropolis_title">Acropolis</string>
    <string name="acropolis_location">Athens, Greece</string>
    <string name="cat_landmark">Landmark</string>
    <string name="soldier_short_desc">The Tomb of the Unknown Soldier is a war memorial located in Syntagma Square in Athens</string>
    <string name="soldier_title">Tomb of the Unknown Soldier</string>
    <string name="soldier_desc">The Tomb of the Unknown soldier is located in Syntagma
        Square in Athens by the Hellenic Parliament building. The tomb honors all those Greek soldiers who were ever killed
        in war and each day, there is a special ceremony performed here that further honors the following.
        While visiting the city, you absolutely don’t want to miss the chance to not only see the tomb itself, but
        to view the ceremony if you are able. The Hellenic Parliament building, however, is more than just the parliament.
        That building has a rich history, as well, since it was the palace when Greece was ruled by a monarchy.</string>
    <string name="soldier_location">Athens, Greece</string>




</resources>
